Gurami Gvanceladze

Tbilisi,

☑ gvanceladze.guga1@gmail.com ☐ +995557905403



I am motivated, hard-working young man With working experience in customer service. I have good communication skills and great language knowledge. I have some skills about Computer and using it everyday. It's like hobby, but every little project helps me to refine my skills. Always trying to learn something new in every detail.

SKILLS

Can do many things at same time Can master new works quickly Copywriting Design Easy to open Fast Good communication Good knowledge Hard-worker Java Mailing Microsoft programms

WORK EXPERIENCE (7)

Dispatcher at Universal-transit

June 2023 - September 2023

It's a different type of dispatching. We are doing our job with only calls. That's helps me to improve my language skills. you need to do 4-5 works at same time and control your time.

Broker at Persati-Logistic November 2022 - May 2023

This job really helps me to improve my seller skills. It's about Trucking. You need to find good carrier company with high rate and buy load from them. Then you need to find Driver and sell this load to him

Dispatcher at Persati-Logistic October 2022 - June 2023

I am dispatcher. Here i need to call drivers to track, also mailing with customers and drivers. We are using Microsoft programms to Description Values

Waiter at Papavero May 2020 - September 2021

This job equals to contact every race of people. It was good to refine your conversational level.

Freelancer at Freelancer - Current

I am doing some jobs from home. Like copywriting, editing, design and some computer programms.

- Current

53 feet, dry vans

Dispatcher at Bravo LLC - Current

53 Feet, Dry vans

EDUCATION (2)

elementary at Copywriting Course

none For now, I am computer science student. at The University of Georgia. - 2021

LANGUAGES

English Russian beginner

INTERESTS -

Draw Freelance Guitar Music Photographing Unusual collection Walking